How fast can you swim?
Rogue is a action, horror, thriller film directed by Greg McLean.
When a group of tourists stumble into the remote Australian river territory of an enormous crocodile, the deadly
creature traps them on a tiny mud island with the tide quickly rising and darkness descending.
As the hungry predator closes in, they must fight for survival against all odds.
Kate Ryan, played by Radha Mitchell.
Pete McKell, played by Michael Vartan.
Neil, played by Sam Worthington.
Mary Ellen, played by Caroline Brazier.
Simon, played by Stephen Curry.
Gwen, played by Celia Ireland.
Rogue is a 2007 horror film written and directed by Greg McLean.
Starring Michael Vartan, Radha Mitchell and Sam Worthington, it follows a group of
tourists in Australia who fall prey to a 7+ metre long saltwater crocodile.
The film was inspired by the true story of Sweetheart, a giant male saltwater crocodile that attacked
boats in the late 1970s, although Sweetheart was never responsible for an attack on a human.
Rogue received positive reviews from critics, but was a commercial failure.
It is the second and last film from Dimension Films to have the involvement of
Village Roadshow Pictures, the other being 1992's Fortress.
The film explores themes of crocodile, tourist, animal
attack, based on true story, wildlife.
The tone is dark and intense.